<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> 
<text comment="This file contains widely used standard phrases for the XML documentation">
    <WebEditing>
        <Elements name="ElementInsertion">
            <para>
            This class should never be instatiated directly. The recommended way to insert an element is to use
            the <see cref="GuruComponents.Netrix.HtmlEditor.Document">Document</see> property of the base class
            <see cref="GuruComponents.Netrix.HtmlEditor"/>. This class provides provides various insertion methods. Each
            method will return an object of type <see cref="GuruComponents.Netrix.WebEditing.Elements.IElement">IElement</see>, 
            which can be casted in the created element (but no other). 
            </para>
        </Elements>
        <Elements name="HorizontalAlign">
        <summary>
        Horizontal alignment (left, center, right) within the surrounding block element.
        </summary>
        <remarks>
        This attributes allows the horizontal alignment within the surrounding block element. The options
        and there behavior differs slightly between the elements. The property allows the list provided
        by the <see cref="System.Web.UI.WebControls.HorizontalAlign">HorizontalAlign</see> enumeration.
        </remarks>
        </Elements>
        <Elements name="TargetAttribute">
            <summary>
            TARGET controls where the new document will be displayed when the user follows a link.
            </summary>
            <remarks>
            Most of the time, clicking on a link simply loads a new document in the same window where the link was. However, with TARGET, you can have the new document open in a new window, or if you are using frames, in another frame. 
            You can target a frame by a name you have assigned it. TARGET also has four predefined values, which can be used as if certain windows and frames already have names without you having to assign them: 
            <list>
                <item>_blank</item>
                <item>_parent</item>
                <item>_self</item>
                <item>_top</item>
            </list>
            A predefined list of targets is provides to the <see cref="System.Windows.Forms.PropertyGrid"/> using the 
            UI assembly (not available in the light edition of NetRix). The base definition can be found in 
            <see cref="System.Web.UI.WebControls.TargetConverter"/>.
            <para>
            Note that each of predefined names starts with an underscore ("_"). They also must be in all lower-case letters. 
            You can also use TARGET with &lt;IFRAME ...&gt; and the NAME attribute.
            </para>
            </remarks>
        </Elements>  
        <Elements name="ColorAttributes">
        <remarks>
        To remove this attribute from the collection of attributes and from the tag definition you can assign
        <see cref="System.Drawing.Color.Empty">Color.Empty</see>. 
        </remarks>
        </Elements>    
        <Elements name="PublicElementConstructor">
            <summary>Internal constructor of the element.</summary>        
            <remarks>
            This constructor supports the NetRix infrastructure and should be used from user code. Various collection editors
            expect public constructors, used to instantiate objects using reflection. The call of this public constructor is
            useless from user code. Use the various insertion method to create and insert new elements instead.
            </remarks>
        </Elements>  
    </WebEditing>
</text>
